DHANANJAY KUMAR SURYESH

CYBER SECURITY TESTER/ANALYST

M dhananjaykumarsuryesh8485@gmail.com ◆+91 8651198892

in LinkedIn

Por

Portfolio

Twitter

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A self-educated Cyber Security analyst with 1 year of expertise in Web/API Pentesting. Driven by a fervor for cyber security and emerging technologies. Contributed to the security of major firms such as **Ring**, **Hubspot**, **Revenuecat**, **Yoti**, **Trendyol**, **Booking.com** etc.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

Year	Degree	Institution/Board	CGPA/%
2020 - 2024	B.E CSE	DSEC, Perambalur Tamil Nadu - 621212	7.74(7 th Sem)
2020	Class – XII	B.R.B College Samastipur, Bihar – 848101	78.2%
2018	Class – X	+2 Janta High School Bazidpur, Samastipur - 848505	68.8%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bug Hunter

2023 – Present

- Finding a security vulnerabilities in public/private programs
- Secured companies like Ring, Revenuecat, Trendyol, etc.

Smart Knower

• Cyber Security Intern

01 June 2022 - 31 July 2022

Oasis Infobyte

• Web Development and Designing

01 Feb 2022 - 28 Feb 2022

PROJECTS

SUBENUM

The Subenum is Subdomain Extractor (Enumeration) tool. It is a Python-based tool designed to simplify the process of discovering subdomains associated with a target domain.

Link: Subenum

WOMEN SAFETY DEVICE WITH ARDUINO

The women safety device has built for helping women & girls, especially in night when women's are travelling alone then they can carry this device, and she will fill uncomfortable then she will press the push button, when she will push button then emergency alert will go on emergency contact with accurate GPS location.

Link: Project

CERTIFICATES

- Web Development training authorized by Oasis infobyte
- Advent Of Cyber 2022 by Try hackme
- SQL Basic by Hacker Rank
- Workshop Certificate of ML & AI by IBM during Cognizance IIT Roorkee tech fest Nov 2022

SKILLS

• Web/API pentesting, Vulnerability Assessment, VAPT OWASP Top 10, Linux.

TOOLS

• Burp Suite Pro, Metasploit, Nmap, Wireshark, FFUF, SQLmap, ghauri, etc.

LANGUAGES

• English Hindi